<table class='w3-table-all w3-card-4' style='color:black;'><td>By:sussteve</td><br /><td>Created:June 21 2024 11:03:42</td><br /></table><table class='w3-table-all w3-card-4' style='color:black;'><td>Using GR8BRIK may seem like an impossible task, but it is really easy. First, I recommend registering an account, as there you can manage models, have a custom username, and secure your account and messages. If you don&#039;t register, GR8BRIK will not let you upload models, or post topics on the Community. You can still comment, but you will be &quot;Anonymous User&quot; and will have a set profile pic (that looks like this: http://www.gr8brik.rf.gd/acc/users/pfps/Anonymous%20User..jpg).

After registering, I recommend watching this video: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4HCCpFntxdk (cool online Lego builder) to get ahold of the Modeler. To start, choose a brick. This can be done by clicking the block icon. There will be 6 bricks that you can select: 1x1 ,2x1, 2x2, 3x1, 3x2, 4x1 and 4x2. Once you have chosen; you can start building. You can change your color by clicking &quot;PAINT&quot; or the paintbrush icon. You can delete by holding &quot;D&quot; and rotate by holding &quot;R&quot;.

Once you&#039;re done, save your model by clicking &quot;Save to device&quot;. If you built everything wrong (somehow) you can click &quot;Delete all&quot;. You can import an existing model by clicking &quot;Load from device&quot;.

After you&#039;re done, you can upload your model (if you&#039;re logged in) by clicking on your username in the right-hand corner. And then finding &quot;Upload model&quot;. Select the .Json model you saved and click &quot;UPLOAD&quot;. The upload should start, and you will see it on the Creations page (and maybe your feed). Good luck using GR8BRIK!</td></table><br /><hr /><table id='7845' class='w3-table-all w3-card-4' style='color:black;'><td><a href='../profile.php?sussteve'><img src='../acc/users/pfps/sussteve..jpg' width='50px' height='50px' style='border-radius:50px'>@susstevedev</a> <b>said:</b><b style='float:right'><a id='7845' href='#7845'>June 21 2024 14:26:39</a></b><br /><p>[b]Test[/b]</p></td></table><br /><table id='5766' class='w3-table-all w3-card-4' style='color:black;'><td><a href='../profile.php?sussteve'><img src='../acc/users/pfps/sussteve..jpg' width='50px' height='50px' style='border-radius:50px'>@susstevedev</a> <b>said:</b><b style='float:right'><a id='5766' href='#5766'>June 21 2024 14:33:38</a></b><br /><p>[b]Tets again[b]</p></td></table><br /><table id='7930' class='w3-table-all w3-card-4' style='color:black;'><td><a href='../profile.php?sussteve'><img src='../acc/users/pfps/sussteve..jpg' width='50px' height='50px' style='border-radius:50px'>@susstevedev</a> <b>said:</b><b style='float:right'><a id='7930' href='#7930'>June 21 2024 14:46:07</a></b><br /><p>5463728</p></td></table><br /><table id='6199' class='w3-table-all w3-card-4' style='color:black;'><td><a href='../profile.php?sussteve'><img src='../acc/users/pfps/sussteve..jpg' width='50px' height='50px' style='border-radius:50px'>@susstevedev</a> <b>said:</b><b style='float:right'><a id='6199' href='#6199'>June 21 2024 14:46:18</a></b><br /><p>[i]Itallics[/i]</p></td></table><br />